Throughout this lesson, I'm going to use examples from a new dataset
خلال هذا الدرس، سأستخدم أمثلة من مجموعة البيانات الجديدة
which contains information about employment levels, life expectancy, GDP,
تحتوي على معلومات عن مستويات التوظيف ومتوسط العمر وإجمالي الناتج المحلي
and school completion rates in various countries.
ومعدلات الإكمال بالمدرسة .في دول مختلفة
This data was collected by the site Gapminder which is linked in
وقد جُمعت هذه البيانات بواسطة الموقع Gapminder المتصل بروابط واردة في
the instructor notes.
.ملاحظات المدرب
In this lesson I won't be going through the data analysis process in order,
،وفي هذا الدرس، لن أتناول عملية تحليل البيانات بالترتيب لأني أريد التركيز على كيفية
since I want to focus on how to use NumPy and Pandas effectively.
استخدام NumPy وPandas .بشكل فعال
Instead you'll be doing a bunch of analysis on this dataset, but
وبدلاً من هذا ستُجري مجموعة من عمليات التحليل بمجموعة البيانات هذه، ولكن
not necessarily in order.
.ليس بالترتيب بالضرورة
I still want you to start off by thinking of some questions though.
ومع ذلك، فلا زلت أرغب في أن تبدأ .بالتفكير في بعض الأسئلة
In the downloadable section there is a file which explains what
وفي القسم القابل للتنزيل يوجد ملف يشرح البيانات المتوفرة
data is available in more detail.
.بمزيد من التفصيل
Take a look at that file and
ألق نظرة أخرى على
try to think of at least five questions that you could answer using this data.
ذلك الملف .وحاول التفكير في خمسة أسئلة على الأقل يمكنك الإجابة عليها باستخدام هذه البيانات
Then share the questions you thought of with your classmates on the forums, and
ثم شارك ما فكرت به من أسئلة مع زملاء حجرة الدراسة والمنتديات وعندما تنتهي
when you're done, check these boxes.
.ضعْ علامات اختيار بهذه المربعات
The csv files containing the actual data are also available in
كما تتوفر أيضًا ملفات بتنسيق csv تحتوي على البيانات الفعلية في القسم القابل للتنزيل
the downloadable section, if you'd like to take a look.
إذا كنت ترغب في إلقاء نظرة .عليها
But that shouldn't be necessary since you'll be able to complete all
ولكن لن يكون هذا ضروريًا لأنك ستتمكن من إكمال جميع تمارين البرمجة
the programming exercises in this lesson within the Udacity editor.
لهذا الدرس . في محرر Udacity